Contact

+918297077222 (Mobile) poojaoct28@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/poojaprabhu-1bb69937 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

MySQL

Programming

Core Java

Languages

Kannada (Native or Bilingual) Konkani (Native or Bilingual) English (Full Professional)

Certifications

Six Sigma Yellow Belt Javascript Basics for Beginners

Honors-Awards

SPOT Award from Deloitte Consulting India Pvt. Ltd. (2015) for delivering Outstanding and Valuable Deliverables to Client

Applause Award from Deloitte Consulting India Pvt. Ltd. (2016) For Contributing towards Client and Business Growth.

SPOT Award from Deloitte Consulting India Pvt. Ltd. (2017) for delivering Outstanding and Valuable Deliverables to Client.

Applause Award from Deloitte Consulting India Pvt. Ltd. (2018) For Contributing towards Client and Business Growth.

Applause Award from Deloitte Consulting India Pvt. Ltd. (2019) For Outstanding and valuable Client Deliverables..

Pooja Prabhu

DC Consultant at Deloitte Consulting India Pvt. Ltd Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

Summary

Pooja is working as DC Consultant in Deloitte Consulting India Pvt. Ltd. for past 5+ years.

Skilled in BizTalk Server, ASP. Net Core, Web API, MVC, JavaScript, Angularjs, MS SQL Data Tools - SSIR, SSIS, SSAS and MS SQL Server and has good domain knowledge on US Public Health sector Industry. B.E. graduate in Information technology major from Savitri Bai Phule University (formerly known as Pune University).

Experience

Deloitte India (Offices of the US)

5 years 7 months

DC Consultant

September 2017 - Present (2 years 11 months)

Bengaluru

Full stack .Net developer

Business Technology Analyst January 2015 - August 2017 (2 years 8 months)

Hyderabad Area, India

Education

Maharshi Karve Stree Shikshan Sanstha's Cummins College Of Engineering For Women

Bachelor of Engineering, Information Technology · (2010 - 2014)

Thakur College of Science and Commerce (TCSC)

Junior College, Science · (2008 - 2010)

St Xaviers High School

SSC · (2005 - 2008)

Chinmaya Higher Primary School, Mangalore

Activity

06/28/2020, Pooja Prabhu added candidate to Senior Software Engineer